https://www.insulspan.com/privacy-policy/

Delta Terms & Conditions
Search our Site...
Insulspan® Privacy Policy
Insulspan is committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology that gives you the most powerful and safe online experience. We realized that there are a lot questions and concerns about what is possible online and how your personal information is being used by the sites you visit.
This Statement of Privacy applies to the Insulspan website and governs data collection and usage. By using the Insulspan website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.
Quick Definitions / FAQ
Personally Identifiable Information: This is data collected which can be directly attributed to you. This information is generally collected to help us provide individual service and to better understand our clients.
Anonymous Information: This is data collected directly by Insulspan or a third-party service, which is not directly attributed to you. This data is generally collected to help Insulspan improve the functionality of the website and the services we provide as a whole.
How Do We Collect Your Email, Name, Address, and Phone Number?
We can only collect this information if you provide it. We can only use this information to contact you, if you grant us permission. We do not sell or give this information to others without your permission.
Can Insulspan Follow or See What I Do on Other Websites?
Insulspan can see how you came to our site; such as through a Google search, an email link, or by typing it into your browser window. This information is usually Anonymous, but may become Personally Identifiable if you willingly submit your information to us (like filling out a form). We can see the last page of the Insulspan site you visited before you leave, but not what site you go to next.
Insulspan may employ third-party tools (such as Google AdWords) to place our ads on external sites that you may visit. While we can generally see which sites send us traffic, and we can see the individual ad you clicked on, we can NEVER attribute your personal information to the site you were on, when you clicked on the ad.
Collection of Your Personal Information
Insulspan collects personally identifiable information, such as your e-mail address, name, address, and telephone number when YOU provide it via an online form located on Insulspan’s website. Insulspan, or one of the third-party tools we use, may also collect anonymous demographic information, which is NOT unique to you, such as your region, age, gender, preferences, and interests.
There is also anonymous information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by Insulspan. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times, and referring website addresses. This information is used by Insulspan to maintain the quality of the website and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Insulspan website.
Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through a blog comment section of the Insulspan website, this information is publicly visible and thus, can be collected and used by outside parties.
Insulspan encourages you to review the privacy statements of the websites you visit, so that you can understand how those websites collect, use, and share your information. Insulspan is not responsible for the privacy statements, or other content, on websites that link to, or mention, the Insulspan website.
Use of Your Personal Information
Insulspan collects and uses your information to operate the Insulspan website and deliver the services you have requested. If you agree to receive email newsletters from Insulspan, Insulspan will use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Insulspan. Insulspan may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.
Insulspan does not sell, rent, or lease its customer lists to third-parties. Insulspan may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) will NOT be transferred to the third-party. In addition, Insulspan may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third-parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Insulspan, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.
Insulspan does not use or disclose sensitive personal information you may provide, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.
Insulspan keeps track of the pages visited within Insulspan website, in order to determine what Insulspan services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising to visitors whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.
The Insulspan website will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Insulspan or its sites; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Insulspan; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Insulspan, or the public.
Use of Cookies
The Insulspan website uses “cookies”. A cookie is a small text file that is placed on your computer’s hard drive by a web page server. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer.
One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you register with the Insulspan site or services, a cookie helps Insulspan to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on.
Insulspan also uses cookies to help us see from where our clients are originating – such as an advertising campaign, web search, or a link from a third-party website. This information is anonymous, but may become Personally Identifiable upon submitting your information on a form within the Insulspan site.
The third-party email program used by Insulspan employs tracking methods. Insulspan tracks “opens” via a tracking pixel in the email – meaning the company can track who opens e-mail messages and when the e-mail messages are opened. The “clicks” are tracked via encoded URLs – meaning when you click on the links contained in our e-mail messages, we can count how many people chose to visit that page from our email. This information is used internally to help us determine the relevance of our messaging and is not shared with any third parties. You can easily unsubscribe from our emails using the link at the bottom of any message we send.
You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Insulspan services or other websites you visit.
Analytics Tools
Insulspan uses analytics tools and other third-party technologies, such as Google Analytics and Bing Analytics, to collect Anonymous information in the form of various user metrics when you visit online sites and/or services. These tools and technologies collect and analyze certain types of information, including pages visited, time on site, referring and exit URLs, onsite behavior and usage information, cookies, IP addresses, device and software identifiers, usage and purchase history, MAC Address, mobile unique device ID, and other similar information.
The third-party analytics companies who collect information on the Insulspan website and/or services and other online products and/or services may combine the information collected with other information they have independently collected from other websites and/or other online or mobile products and services relating to your activities across their network of websites as well as online and/or mobile products and services. Many of these companies collect and use information under their own privacy policies.
In addition to Insulspan’s use of technologies as described herein, the company may permit certain third-party companies to help tailor advertising that they think may be of interest to you based on your use of the Insulspan website or services, and to otherwise collect and use data about your use of Insulspan website or services. For more information about this practice, please see the “Third Party Advertising Technologies” section below.
Advertising & Third Party Advertising Technologies
Insulspan may use your Anonymous information, including behavioral metrics, geo-location data, demographic data, website history, and marketing preferences to personalize and display advertisements, and other content for you.
In addition to using cookies and related technologies as described above, Insulspan also may permit certain third-party companies to help tailor advertising that they think may be of interest to users, and to collect and use other Anonymous data about user activities on its sites and/or services (e.g., to allow them to tailor ads on third-party services). These companies may deliver ads that might also place cookies and otherwise track user behavior. These companies may use information about user behavior in order to provide customized advertisements across various services and products. In the course of providing these services, products, or placing advertisements, these third-party companies may place or recognize a unique cookie on your computer, and may record information to these cookies based upon your activities on the Insulspan site, and on third-party websites. Each of these companies uses this cookie information according to their own privacy and security policies. If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you targeted ads, you may opt-out as indicated in this Policy. Please note this does not opt you out of being delivered advertising. You will continue to receive generic ads.
Security of Your Personal Information
Insulspan secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. Insulspan secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment protected from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol. No personally identifiable information is stored on our webserver.
Changes to This Statement
Insulspan will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. Insulspan encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Insulspan is protecting your information.
Contact Information
Insulspan welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that Insulspan has not adhered to this Statement, please contact Insulspan at insulspan@insulspan.com. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.
SIGN UP FOR OUR NEWSLETTER TODAY!
Sign Up
Insulspan is part of PFB Corporation, a publicly traded company listed on the Toronto Stock Exchange that was founded in 1968. When you work with Insulspan, rest assured that you are working with a financially stable company that produces sustainable, high-quality products through adherence to our core values of quality, service, and expertise.
Our Advantages
Superior Energy Efficiency
Health & Comfort
Strength, Flexibility & Quality
Speed of Construction
Insulspan Products
SIP Panel Cost: SIPs v Stick Frame
EPS Insulation vs Polyurethane Insulation
INSULSPAN Structural Insulating Panel System. All rights reserved.
800.726.3510  EAST, MIDWEST
|
866.848.8855  WEST
